// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which pronoun would best replace Dora and Ahmed in the following sentence? Dora and Ahmed collected bottles.",
    answer: "They",
    options: [
      "They",
      "Them",
      "That",
      "Those"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "I saw Mr. Brown this morning. I gave _____ my homework.",
    answer: "Him",
    options: [
      "He",
      "Him",
      "She",
      "They"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "John likes computer games.____ plays ________ very often.",
    answer: "He,Them",
    options: [
      "She,Them",
      "She,It",
      "He,Them",
      "He,It"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "My mother____the breakfast in the kitchen",
    answer: "prepares",
    options: [
      "preparing",
      "prepares",
      "will",
      "will not"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Sorry, you can't borrow my pencil. I ______ it myself.",
    answer: "am using",
    options: [
      "will use",
      "uses",
      "used",
      "am using"
    ]
  }, 
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Suzy _______ a cake at the bakery afterwards.",
      answer: "will buy",
      options: [
      "will buy",
      "buys",
      "buying",
      "bought"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "The children ________ so much noise.",
      answer: "are making",
      options: [
      "makes",
      "are making",
      "making",
      "is making"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "My sister _______ when the phone rang.",
      answer: "was cooking",
      options: [
      "is cooking",
      "are cooking",
      "were cooking",
      "was cooking"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "eat",
      answer: "Present Simple",
      options: [
      "Present Perfect",
      "Past Simple",
      "Past Perfect",
      "Present Simple"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which verb is NOT in the past tense?",
      answer: "He works.",
      options: [
      "He works.",
      "He walked.",
      "He went.",
      "He bought."
    ]
  },


  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];